I just walked into a store,
sold seven vei,
more sold why?
Because the Brigadier is good.
Nobody even knows if my Passenger is good,
because I have a lot of people
who will sell Passenger and talk, ah
as if he were a victim hand,
oh,
my husband is unemployed,
i need to pay for college
and that's why I'm here selling theiro,
bro,
to victimize yourself old,
exchange 1 idea,
you don't need it,
it's not on,
arrives,
talks to people,
gives 1 good day,
look in the eye
and speaks a real veil,
says you're there to be able to give her a benefit
it gets easier,
old this is adding up on one's day,
this one is the most important thing.
Now I will
let's see this store next door
and let's take a look there
How are you?
Oh, turn on,
take 1 look.